drdrebeatsheadphones-australia.com 2012-01-19

# Privacy Notice :

**Privacy Policy**

**How can we protect your privacy?**  
The security of your personal information is very important to us. We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances. We value your trust very highly, and will work to protect the security and privacy of any personal information you provide to us and will only use it as we have described in our Privacy Policy.

**What personal information do we collect?**  
As set forth in more detail below, We collects personal information that you provide when using the internet-shoping web site ("Site"). This information includes your first and last name, email address and phone number when you create your account. You can browse this Site without creating an account, but you will need to create an account when you purchase something and in order to take advantage of tracking the order and the other services of our webiste. We may ask you to confirm your personal information when you contact our Customer Service department. This will allow us to protect your confidentiality by verifying your identity.  
Internet-shoping does not intentionally collect personal information about children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 18 but at least 13 years of age you may use this Site only under the supervision of a parent or legal guardian who agrees to be bound by the our website'sTerms of Use. 

**Security**  
Our website uses industry standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is required. This encryption technology protects your name, address, and credit card number during data transport. We proudly displays the Verified Secure Seal - Our website has been scanned using the Control Scan Verified Secure vulnerability scanner for over 11000 vulnerabilities. This site is tested weekly and on demand to pass the FBI/SANS Internet Security Test.

**Our website is:**  
99.9% FREE from Hacker crime. Tested for thousands of vulnerabilities including the FBI/SANS TOP 20.  
Notified immediately of any new vulnerabilities that may arise.  
Safe from identity theft and credit card fraud.  
In compliance with the Gramm Leach-Bliley, Children's Privacy, HIPAA, and Sarbanes Oxley Acts.
